Welcome back to APUS History in under 3
minutes. No time for intros, let's get
into it. Topic 1.6 is all about
different views in the world during this
time, along with some organized military
resistances. So, it's fair to say that
anytime in history when an existing
culture interacts with a new culture,
misinterpretations and profiling will
always happen from both sides. In terms
of the natives and Europeans, their
cultures had different worldviews on
religion, gender roles, family, land
use, and power. Over time, Europeans and
Native Americans adopted some useful
aspects of each others culture. But, as
Europeans increasingly attempted to
enslave the natives, different military
defenses from the natives happened. A
few examples of this were the Capulana
Uprising in the Yucatan and the Taino
Rebellion in the Caribbean. And even
though documents like the Requerimiento
tried to justify harsh treatment of the
natives, it sparked debates from around
the continent of how Africans and Native
Americans should be treated. Though
these arguments did exist, any arguments
often led to Europeans justifying their
treatment of Africans and the natives
using culture or race as an answer.
Unfortunately, that is most of what
early US history is about. On the screen
now are AP style questions for this
topic. Pause now.
I'll put the work and answers on the
screen now.
See you in the next one.